Die, dog emperor!
Protect His Majesty!
Han'er, here.
Daoist Master,
Meng Qian,
escort His Majesty first.
Your Majesty.
Catch the sword!
Zhu Zitong!
How are you?
Lord Chu.
I'm afraid
I can no longer
protect you
in the future, My Lord.
Zhu Zitong!
My Lord.
Father,
the candy is so sweet.
She looks
so much like my daughter.
His Majesty is fine.
Your Majesty.
My brothers in Liangshan
are willing to surrender to the imperial court.
This is the letter of surrender
written by my brother Gongming himself.
Please take a look, Your Majesty.
That the Liangshan brothers
can realize their errors
and sincerely surrender
makes me very pleased.
Mr. Zhou.
If we can escort His Majesty down the West Tower,
will there be reinforcements?
Even if the guards downstairs are completely wiped out,
as long as the signal fire is lit,
the Imperial City Division will arrive in a quarter of an hour at most.
May I ask where the fireworks are?
On the first floor,
the leftmost room.
Okay.
Then His Majesty
is left to Mr. Zhou and the Taoist Master.
Please.
The Zhao Song royal family favors corrupt officials and sycophants.
Endless wars
have displaced the common people,
causing unspeakable suffering.
Will your Liangshan
really make an enemy of us Shedao people for this man?
The matter of surrender
was a choice made by all the brothers of Liangshan.
Regardless of right or wrong,
our Liangshan
has a clear conscience.
What a clear conscience!
You!
Your Majesty.
Guards!
Somebody, hurry!
Meng Qian,
go set off the signal.
Hurry!
Sister.
Why are you doing this?